ominent.com 2014-09-22

# Ominent

### Ominent Privacy Policy

**Tuvaro, Inc., d/b/a Ominent ("Ominent") respects your privacy.** This Privacy Policy has been prepared to describe the information we collect about you, how it is used, and with whom we may or may not share it. This Privacy Policy covers the Ominent website, along with any and all related websites (including blogs), and any website registration, survey and polling pages that we may create for other entities.

This Privacy Policy applies to Ominent services only, and does not apply to any sites not controlled by Ominent that may link to or from the Ominent website or any third-party applications, gadgets or clickable advertisements on our site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other such parties / sites. We do not exercise control over the sites that appear as search results when you use the Ominent website.

### Your Information and Our Use

In order to provide you with our technology, we may collect the following types of information:

  * Personal Information: When you register for an account, your name, title, company, email address, mailing address and other personally identifying information (collectively, "Personally Identifiable Information"), in addition to other demographic data, will be retained in order to allow you to use your account. It is our policy to use Personally Identifiable Information to provide our technology and services, and not provide such to anyone outside of Ominent without your consent (but see "Exceptions to this Privacy Policy" below).
  * Submitted Material: When you use the Ominent website and functionality, you will provide certain materials and content. As you participate in the website, you will also provide certain information regarding such participation to us. As a reminder, whenever you share information on Ominent in your profile, in public areas, or with specific individuals, such information can be viewed by such persons.
  * Public Content: If you provide content to Ominent for public view, we may distribute that content to a wider audience by sharing it (or portions of it) with third parties so that they can publish it on their websites and other media platforms. Ominent may, in some instances, ask that such third parties credit you as the source of these contributions, and will provide your account name and profile photo, if any, to them for such purpose.
  * Website Visit Information: When you visit our website, we may create a log of your visit with information, which includes information such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, URL information, browser type and language, and the date, time and duration of your visit.
  * Links: The Ominent website may present links in a format that permits us to track whether these links have been followed. We will use this tracking information to help improve the quality of our custom content, search technology and advertising.
  * Cookies: When you visit our website, we may send cookies (little files for your browser that identify your browser and your visit). Ominent also uses cookies in its advertising services in order to help publishers and advertisers manage and provide advertising across the web. We are working with third-party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver in-text and overlay contextual ads. We do not share your non-public personal information with these third parties, but we may share anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see. As noted above, these third-party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. 
  * Communications: If you send us emails, faxes, letters or other communications, we may keep these in order to address your issue

The information we collect, as described above, will be used pursuant to this Privacy Policy, and for the following purposes: to improve our services and products; to develop new services; to ensure and improve the technical functionality of our website and network; to protect your rights, Ominent's rights and the rights of other Ominent users; and to assist Ominent in providing you with services (including customizing the content and advertising provided to you).

### Survey and Polling Pages

Ominent regularly designs and hosts online registration, survey and polling pages. On each page, we collect specific demographic data about registrants, as requested by the client or event sponsors of such pages. Ominent routinely provides this demographic data at the request of the client or event sponsors. Any demographic information collected by Ominent on behalf of a client or event sponsor is the property of that entity, and Ominent employees and agents will not share this information except as required to adequately provide services to that client or event sponsor. Ominent will not sell or provide any information to a third party, including other clients that may employ the services of Ominent.

### Blogs

Ominent may host blogs or search field topics that gather visitor demographic data including names and email addresses. Ominent may use this information to provide updates about our website and our services. Ominent will not resell or provide this information to any third-party vendors.

### Exceptions to this Privacy Policy

In certain circumstances, Ominent may release the information it collects, for the following purposes:

  * To respond to court orders, subpoenas, or other legal process, or to help Ominent in establishing or exercising its legal rights or defend itself against legal claims;
  * To investigate, prevent or take action with regard to illegal activity, suspected fraud, potential threat to the physical safety of any individual, violations of the Ominent Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law;
  * To investigate or take action with respect to any circumstance that could expose Ominent to liability; and
  * If Ominent is acquired by or merges with another company. In this event, Ominent will notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Ominent may also share non-personal information about you, in the aggregate, to third parties.

### Our Policy Toward Children

The Ominent website is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children younger than thirteen years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

### Dispute Resolution

If you believe that Ominent has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Tuvaro  
Attention: Legal Department  
PO Box 7775, San Francisco, CA 94120-7775 

If we receive any formal complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, we will seek to contact you to address your concerns.

**Note:** This address is provided exclusively for notifying us about the Privacy Policy. Inquiries regarding any other topics, such as technical support requests, reports concerning email abuse, and reports of instances of piracy, will not receive a response through this process.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Ominent may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address you have specified in your Ominent account or by placing a prominent notice on the Ominent website.

### Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using this website, or by submitting demographic information on any online pages that Ominent may host on behalf of third parties, you submit your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
